yourlisten.com 2019-12-08

# Privacy Policy | YourListen

Your privacy means a lot to us! Our Privacy Policy is here to inform you how we gather, place, use and disclose your information when you use YourListen.com, and all related services.

By using and registering with YourListen.com, you are consenting to the use of your personal information in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. 

## Data Protection and Privacy

All information is collected, stored and used in accordance with our Privacy Policy. Read below to ensure you understand how our privacy policy works.

By accepting our Terms of Use and using YourListen.com you also accept the terms of the Privacy Policy. 

When you register with YourListen.com you will need a user name, password and email address. It is your responsibility to keep all of your registration data up to date. All registration information provided falls under the terms set forth in the YourListen.com Privacy Policy. If your username or password is lost or stolen or think your account has been compromised first change your username and password then contact us at: support@yourlisten.com

## Information collected about you

You do not need to provide us any information when visiting the site. The only time we collect information from you is when you register for an account. We do not contract with a data processing company. 

When you register for an account we will only collect your user name, password and email that you register with. This information is mandatory to create an account. All other information you provide on your profile is optional. What information you provide publicly on our site is also controlled by you. You have full control over your data.

There is some information we collect upon visiting YourListen.com. This data is collected via cookies and Google analytics.

**We collect the ip address from the device you visit the site on:**

  1. The site you visited before coming to YourListen.com
  2. Audio files you upload
  3. Which other users you follow and which users follow you
  4. Connection of your facebook account
  5. The time, frequency and duration of your visits to the Website
  6. Your browser type and operating system

If you are visiting the site from outside the United States, please be aware that you are sending information (including Personal Data) to the United States and Canada, where our servers are located. That information may be transferred within the United States or back out of the United States to other countries outside of your country of residence, depending on the type of information and how it is stored by us. These countries (including the United States) may not necessarily have data protection laws as comprehensive or protective as those in your country of residence; however, our collection, storage, and use of your Personal Data will at all times continue to be governed by this Privacy Policy.

Personal Data transfers may fall under legal frameworks such as the EU-US Privacy Shield as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from the European Union countries.

For EU members, we comply with the EU Data Protection Directive 95/46/EC framwork as set forth by the European Union regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland. We adhere to the requirements of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement.

Google collects information about you to provide use with statistics and analytics about our traffic. They have a separate privacy policy, which you may want to review.

Much of this information may be non-personally identifiable. We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, et.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain services and those of our partners. Our partners also have the option to publish the results for their websites. 

You may request a copy of the information we have about you and/or request that your information be deleted by emailing us at: support@yourlisten.com We keep your information as long as you have an account with us. 

We use cookies to make your experience better. These cookies make it possible for you to login and logout of the website. They also allow the website to remember your preferences. 

We also use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This enables us to view data about web page traffic and improve our site for you. You can refuse to accept cookies by enabling the setting on your computer. If you decide on to do so you may be unable to access bound components of our web site. Our advertisers may use cookies over that we have no management.

Your email address will be used to send you newsletters and email notifications for uploads and follows. To unsubscribe from newsletters and email notifications email us at support@yourlisten.com

## Your Information

You can control access to other services and applications to which you have connected your account to YourListen.com.

Information in your profiles except for your email will be accessible by other users on YourListen.com. We do, however, provide you with an option to make particular information in your profile private.

If required by law we will disclose your YourListen.com information.

We may share your personal information with third parties for marketing purposes. 

## Third-Party Ad Servers

We use third party advertising companies to target and serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use cookies and other tracking technologies to serve as relevant of ads to you as possible.

Our website might have links to third party websites. When you click a link and leave to a third party website we are not responsible for the protection of your privacy and our privacy policy does not govern. 

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp]()

## Facebook Registrations

YourListen.com allows you to sign up and log in using your Facebook account. If you register with Facebook, Facebook will confirm that you give permission to share particular information from your Facebook account with YourListen.com.

This information is collected by Facebook and is provided to us under the terms of Facebook's privacy policy. You are in control of what we receive from Facebook using the privacy settings in your Facebook account.

You can also control the activities you perform on YourListen.com that we send to Facebook. 

## Children

YourListen.com is not intended for use by children. Anyone under the age of 16 (sixteen) is not permitted to use the site or register for an account. If it comes to our attention that we have collected personal data from a person under the age of 16 (sixteen), we will terminate your account.

## Privacy Statement

If you are concerned about how your information is collected or used you need to occasionally check on our Privacy Policy. If you have any other concerns not mentioned in the Policy, please contact us using our support email which is support@yourlisten.com

If you choose to not provide your consent, or if you withdraw your authorization, you should not use the website as a registered user, since many of the website's features are based on users consent. 

## Alterations and Updates to our Privacy Policy

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. Modifications to our Privacy Policy will be available here on our Privacy Policy page.

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or want to suggest changes to this Privacy Policy email us at support@yourlisten.com

How we protect your information: We are concerned with protecting your privacy and data, but we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to YourListen or guarantee that your information on the website may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of any of our industry standard physical, technical or managerial safeguards. When you enter sensitive information (such as login credentials) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). No method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any question about security on our Site, you can contact us at the email below. We use an outside credit card processing company to bill you if you purchase services. These companies do not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

You can contact us at any time to:  

  1. Request access to information that we have about you
  2. Correct any information that we have about you
  3. Delete information that we have about you

If you have any additional questions about the collection and storage of data, please contact us at: support@yourlisten.com or PO Box 3375, Redondo Beach, CA, USA, 90277. Ph 323-999-4856
